<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Home on The Miata Finder Blog</title>
    <link>https://finder.miata.cc/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Home on The Miata Finder Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-gb</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 06 Feb 2024 17:25:54 -0500</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://finder.miata.cc/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>A Small Update (NA)</title>
      <link>https://finder.miata.cc/posts/2024-02-06/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Feb 2024 17:25:54 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finder.miata.cc/posts/2024-02-06/</guid>
      
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Those who know me personally, know that I got rear-ended in my Miata (damage pictured below). This happened a few days before Thanksgiving of 2023. So because of that, the driving of my NA was brought down to once a month (just so I know it still works).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I should be taking my NA to get repaired in the coming weeks after getting a big delay. I wanted to post an updated without finding another Miata. I feel like this would go against the spirit of the website. Luckily I found one today, a white 1989 NA.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Once again my brother was with me and we did our thing. We had planned to leave when the polaroid we took developed (and leave it on the car) but we were happy to see that the owner came out and we had a small chat. He told us that he had two Miatas and he only drove the white NA today because it had been sitting for months. He showed us his pictures of his other Miata (also a NA) and we gave him the polaroid we took. Unfortunately we didn’t get to take a picture of the polaroid, but below are the pictures I normally take with the Sony Mavica.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://finder.miata.cc/24-02-06-NA-1.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;NA 1&#34;&gt;
&lt;img src=&#34;https://finder.miata.cc/24-02-06-NA-2.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;NA 2&#34;&gt;
&lt;img src=&#34;https://finder.miata.cc/24-02-06-NA-3.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;NA 3&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>First Sighting (NC)</title>
      <link>https://finder.miata.cc/posts/2023-11-09/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Nov 2023 22:15:42 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finder.miata.cc/posts/2023-11-09/</guid>
      
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Today was the lucky day where I finally found my first Miata!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I found myself an Silver 2008 NC while driving with my brother.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This being my first encounter I wanted to just take the pictures and leave, however my brother suggested that we should stay and talk to the owner. Im glad I did wait as the conversation we had was wonderful and hearing her talk about her Miata made me proud to be an owner of one as well.
She had talked to us about how she had been run off the road in her Miata but despite that the NC was shining!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This is only the second time I have seen an NC up close and seeing the differances and similarities was cool.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Here are the pictures I took on my beloved Sony Mavica, and of course the polaroid I took of them. The worst picture is sadly the polaroid, thats just something that Im gonna have to get better at.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://finder.miata.cc/23-11-09-NC-1.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;NC 1&#34;&gt;
&lt;img src=&#34;https://finder.miata.cc/23-11-09-NC-2.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;NC 2&#34;&gt;
&lt;img src=&#34;https://finder.miata.cc/23-11-09-NC-3.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;NC 3&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://finder.miata.cc/pages/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Oct 2023 16:38:20 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finder.miata.cc/pages/about/</guid>
      
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;welcome-to-the-miata-finder-blog&#34;&gt;Welcome To The Miata Finder Blog!&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Here you will find me posting pictures of my 1991 Miata (pictured below) alongside other Miata (sometimes any Mazda car!).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This idea was started by my brother who suggested we leave polaroids when we park next to other Miatas. I really liked that idea and decided to take it one step further by creating this blog.
Thanks for checking out my blog.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You can contact me via email at &lt;a href=&#34;mailto:ubaldo@nopal.cc&#34;&gt;ubaldo@nopal.cc&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://finder.miata.cc/my-miata.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;my miata&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This blog currently uses the &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/hugo-sid/hugo-blog-awesome&#34;&gt;Hugo Blog Awesome Blog&lt;/a&gt;. I plan to make my own theme for this website at somepoint, so look out for that in the future.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
      
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
